# **SOHYE LEE**

and UX/UI design.

Fairfax, VA

571-396-1662



sohye.dev

github.com/sohye-lee \_

sohyelee@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sohyelee

## <sup>•</sup> in

PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS | www.sohye.dev

## **FULL STACK BLOGGING PLATFORM**

React | Express | NodeJS | MongoDB

Completed <u>full stack</u> development for responsive <u>blog website</u> enabling users to register and author personal blogs. Implemented features including separate access for administrator and user/writer, as well as authentication.

Motivated and passionate full stack developer. Former experience in dynamic, fast -paced

environments. Self-motivated with ability to learn quickly and deep interest in data management

## **FULL STACK E-COMMMERCE STORE**

React | Express | NodeJS | MongoDB

Oversaw <u>full stack</u> development of fully responsive <u>e-commerce website</u> for bag sellers, implementing <u>authentication</u>, separate access for seller and customer, and PayPal payment acceptance.

## **FULLY RESPONSIVE LANDING PAGE & APP**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Bootstrap | React Native

Designed engaging front end of website and mobile application for salad delivery shop, as well as integrating **bright/dark color mode change** with simple button click to improve user experience.

LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGIES

FRONT END. BACK END TOOLS & OTHERS

React NodeJS Github
React Native Express VS Code
JavaScript(ES6) MongoDB Adobe XD

Python GraphQL-Apollo Adobe Photoshop Plotly Django Adobe Illustrator

Bootstrap TypeScript

HTML5, CSS3 SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### WEB DEVELOPER, FULL STACK INTERN

WEBSITE INNOVATOR

Rockville, MD | 2021 - current

- Deliver fully responsive and customized landing page website
- <u>Communicate with clients</u> to discuss timelines and manage expectations. Complete project planning, establish workflows, and prioritize assignments to ensure client retention and customer satisfaction.

#### ART COLLECTION DATA DEVELOPER

**ELAND WORLD LIMITED** 

Seoul, S. Korea | 2013 - 2016

- <u>Developed and implemented new collection database</u>, significantly improving data structure and enriching content with further research and writing.
- Collaborated with archive team to outline project scope and establish optimal data and filing systems for collection of +300K items.

## MUSEUM COLLECTION MANAGER & REGISTRAR

SEOUL MUSEUM OF ART

Seoul, S. Korea | 2011 - 2013

- Oversaw care and preservation of artifacts, completing accurate reporting and daily entries. Updated and maintained system data, conducting research and ensuring all collection information up to date.
- Drove project management of catalog publications, scheduling tasks, coordinating stakeholders, and ensuring publication within strict timelines.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Master in Data Analytics

Georgia Institute of Technology (remote / currently enrolled) 2023

#### **Bachelor in Computer Science**

Korean National Accredited e-Green Cyber Education Center (remote) 2021

#### Master in Museum Studies

Ecole Du Louvre Paris | France 2008

#### **Bachelor in Art History**

Ecole Du Louvre Paris | France 2006

#### **Bachelor of Fine Arts**

Seoul National University Seoul | S. Korea 2001

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Full Stack Web and Mobile Development Bootcamp Certificate of Honor

Nucamp 2021

Professional Certificate: Introduction to Python Programming

Georgia Tech @ EDX

#### **LANGUAGES**

Korean Englsh French

Chinese